planisware.com 2011-03-13

# Planisware: Privacy Policy

Select your country / language   

Planisware is committed to protecting your privacy online. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at the planisware.com Web site. 

**The Information We Collect**   
When you visit our site, we may collect personally identifiable information, including name address and email address. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

**How We Use the Information**   
We use the information you provide about yourself to respond to your inquiries about our products and services, and if you opted in to send you news and updates about our offerings to provide you with opportunities to purchase other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We will disclose personally identifiable information only in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products or services. 

**Cookies**   
We use "cookies" to enhance your experience with our site. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. We do not use our cookies to determine any personally identifiable information about you. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web page (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products or services. 

**Opt-Out**   
We communicate with users who request information about our products and services on a regular basis via email, and we may also communicate by phone to follow up on information requests or resolve potential issues. We may use your email address to send you information about changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. 

Planisware provides you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive other types of communication from us such as emails or updates from us regarding new services and products offered on this Web site. The opt-out choice may be exercised by unsubscribing. We will process your unsubscribe as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed. 

**Contact Us**   
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy or its implementation, you may contact through our web formular or by phone at your nearest Planisware location. See our contact page.
